{"questions":[{"answers":{"Dose (mg)":["25 QD"],"Max Dose (mg)":["100 QD"],"Brand":["Thalitone"]},"questionText":"Chlorthalidone"},{"answers":{"Dose (mg)":["12.5-50 QD"],"Max Dose (mg)":["50 QD"],"Brand ":["MAcrozide"]},"questionText":"HCTZ"},{"answers":{"Dose (mg)":["10-40 QD"],"Max Dose (mg)":["40 QD"],"Brand ":["Prinivil, Zestril, Qbrelis"]},"questionText":"Lisinopril"},{"answers":{"Dose (mg)":["5-40 QD-BID"],"Max Dose (mg)":["40 QD"],"Brand ":["Vasotec"]},"questionText":"Enalapril "},{"answers":{"Dose (mg)":["2.5-10 QD-BID"],"Max Dose (mg)":["20 QD"],"Brand ":["Altace"]},"questionText":"Ramipril "},{"answers":{"Dose (mg)":["25-100 QD-BID"],"Max Dose (mg)":["100 QD"],"Brand ":["Cozaar"]},"questionText":"Losartan"},{"answers":{"Dose (mg)":["80-320 QD"],"Max Dose (mg)":["320 QD"],"Brand ":["Diovan"]},"questionText":"Valsartan"},{"answers":{"Dose (mg)":["2.5-10 QD"],"Max Dose (mg)":["10 QD"],"Brand ":["Norvasc"]},"questionText":"Amlodipine"},{"answers":{"Dose (mg)":["30-90 QD"],"Max Dose (mg)":["180QD"],"Brand ":["Adalat, Procardia"]},"questionText":"Nifedipine"},{"answers":{"Dose (mg)":["120-360 QD-BID"],"Max Dose (mg)":["Varies"],"Brand ":["Cardizem CD, Cartia, Taxtia, Tiadylt, Tiazac"]},"questionText":"Diltiazem CER"},{"answers":{"Dose (mg)":["120-360 QD-BID"],"Max Dose (mg)":["Varies"],"Brand ":["Cardizem LA"]},"questionText":"Diltiazem TER"},{"answers":{"Dose (mg)":["240-480 TID-QID"],"Max Dose (mg)":["Varies"],"Brand ":["Calan"]},"questionText":"Verapamil IR"},{"answers":{"Dose (mg)":["240-480 QD-BID"],"Max Dose (mg)":["Varies"],"Brand ":["Calan SR"]},"questionText":"Verapamil TER\/CR"},{"answers":{"Dose (mg)":["240-480 QD-BID"],"Max Dose (mg)":["Varies"],"Brand ":["Verelan"]},"questionText":"Verapamil CER"},{"answers":{"Dose (mg)":["20-40 BID"],"Max Dose (mg)":["160 QD"],"Brand ":["Lasix"]},"questionText":"Furosemide"},{"answers":{"Dose (mg)":["25-100 QD"],"Max Dose (mg)":["100 QD"],"Brand ":["Aldactone"]},"questionText":"Spironolactone"},{"answers":{"Dose (mg)":["50-100 QD-BID"],"Max Dose (mg)":["200 QD"],"Brand ":["Dyreneium"]},"questionText":"Triamteren"},{"answers":{"Dose (mg)":["25-100 QD"],"Max Dose (mg)":["100 QD"],"Brand ":["Tenormin"]},"questionText":"Atenolol"},{"answers":{"Dose (mg)":["25-100 BID"],"Max Dose (mg)":["200 QD"],"Brand ":["Lopressor"]},"questionText":"Metoprolol tartrate"},{"answers":{"Dose (mg)":["12.5-200 QD"],"Max Dose (mg)":["200 QD"],"Brand ":["Toprol XL"]},"questionText":"Metoprolol succinate"},{"answers":{"Dose (mg)":["40-160 BID"],"Max Dose (mg)":["320 QD"],"Brand ":["Inderal"]},"questionText":"Propranolol IR "},{"answers":{"Dose (mg)":["80-160 QD"],"Max Dose (mg)":["160 QD"],"Brand ":["Inderal LA, InnoPran XL"]},"questionText":"Propranolol LA"},{"answers":{"Dose (mg)":["3.125-50 BID"],"Max Dose (mg)":["25 <=85Kg, 50 >85Kg"],"Brand ":["Coreg"]},"questionText":"Carvedilol"},{"answers":{"Dose (mg)":["20-80 QD"],"Max Dose (mg)":["80 QD"],"Brand ":["Coreg CR"]},"questionText":"Carvedilol PO4"},{"answers":{"Dose (mg)":["100-1200 BID"],"Max Dose (mg)":["2400 QD"],"Brand ":["Trandate, Normodyne "]},"questionText":"Labetalol"},{"answers":{"Dose (mg)":["1-8 QD"],"Max Dose (mg)":["16 QD"],"Brand ":["Cardura"]},"questionText":"Doxazosin"},{"answers":{"Dose (mg)":["1-5 BID-TID"],"Max Dose (mg)":["15 QD"],"Brand ":["Minipress"]},"questionText":"Prazosin"},{"answers":{"Dose (mg)":["0.1-0.3 BID-TID"],"Max Dose (mg)":["0.8 QD"],"Brand ":["Catapres"]},"questionText":"Clonidine"},{"answers":{"Dose (mg)":["0.1-0.3 QWEEK"],"Max Dose (mg)":["0.3 QWEEK"],"Brand ":["Catapres"]},"questionText":"Clonidine Patch"},{"answers":{"Dose (mg)":["10-50 TID-QID"],"Max Dose (mg)":["200 QD"],"Brand ":["-1"]},"questionText":"Hydralazine "}],"answerCols":["Brand ","Dose (mg)","Max Dose (mg)"],"questionAsk":"Generic ","title":"HTN_Dosage_List","rows":30}